Connecting to database...
Fetching metadata...
Cleaning existing reports for 2026-04-07...
Starting seed loop...

Results: 108 reports created.

Collisions (Duplicates resolved): 2
 - COLLISION: Input "Dhaka Community Medical College Hospital" and previously mapped record both matched to DB Facility "Dhaka Community Medical college Hospital" in Dhaka
 - COLLISION: Input "General Medical College & Hospital" and previously mapped record both matched to DB Facility "Hi-Care General Hospital Ltd." in Dhaka

Unmatched facilities (11):
Dr. M R Khan shishu Hospital & Institute of Child Health, Mirpur-2, Dhaka (Dhaka), Dr. Sirajul Islam Medical College & Hospital Ltd. (Dhaka), Holy Family Red Crescent Medical College Hopital (Dhaka), Insaf Barakah Kidney & General Hospital (Dhaka), Popular Medical College And Hospital Ltd. (Dhaka), Z H Sikder Women's Medical College & Hospital (pvt) Ltd., Gulshan. (Dhaka), Ata Khan Medical College & Hospital (Dhaka), Shanto-Mariam General Hospital (Dhaka), Impulse Hospital (Dhaka), Pan Pacific Hospital (Dhaka), South Ridge Hospital (Dhaka)
